[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Detroit", "Appalachia", "Newtown"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "Day one, President Obama's second term, can he keep his promises to America on guns after another school shooting today?", "question_tokens": ["Day", "one", ",", "President", "Obama", "'s", "second", "term", ",", "can", "he", "keep", "his", "promises", "to", "America", "on", "guns", "after", "another", "school", "shooting", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "Our journey is not complete until all our children from the streets of Detroit, to the hills of Appalachia, to the quiet lanes of Newtown, know that they are cared for and cherished and always safe from harm.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "journey", "is", "not", "complete", "until", "all", "our", "children", "from", "the", "streets", "of", "Detroit", ",", "to", "the", "hills", "of", "Appalachia", ",", "to", "the", "quiet", "lanes", "of", "Newtown", ",", "know", "that", "they", "are", "cared", "for", "and", "cherished", "and", "always", "safe", "from", "harm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "My understanding is you have armed police specifically employed at the school and also civilian security, but they're not armed, is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["My", "understanding", "is", "you", "have", "armed", "police", "specifically", "employed", "at", "the", "school", "and", "also", "civilian", "security", ",", "but", "they", "'re", "not", "armed", ",", "is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I think some of them are.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "some", "of", "them", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What was your reading of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reading", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I think we have a different tone from President Obama than we've had in the past.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "a", "different", "tone", "from", "President", "Obama", "than", "we", "'ve", "had", "in", "the", "past", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "How successful can he be with the kind of quite ambitious plans that he laid out yesterday for what he wants to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["How", "successful", "can", "he", "be", "with", "the", "kind", "of", "quite", "ambitious", "plans", "that", "he", "laid", "out", "yesterday", "for", "what", "he", "wants", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, as we sit here tonight, I think it's limited what he can achieve.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "we", "sit", "here", "tonight", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "limited", "what", "he", "can", "achieve", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Do you like the tenor of what you're hearing from him for his second term or is it fiddling while Rome burns?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "tenor", "of", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", "from", "him", "for", "his", "second", "term", "or", "is", "it", "fiddling", "while", "Rome", "burns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "No, first of all, I don't think America's in bad shape at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "America", "'s", "in", "bad", "shape", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rome"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "How can a country that's so riddled with debt actually not be in bad shape?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "a", "country", "that", "'s", "so", "riddled", "with", "debt", "actually", "not", "be", "in", "bad", "shape", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, first of all, you know, when we talk about debt, everybody likes to compare it to households.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "we", "talk", "about", "debt", ",", "everybody", "likes", "to", "compare", "it", "to", "households", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["8 percent"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What is the answer to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "answer", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Perhaps that's true, but if you're one of the 8 percent who are unemployed and are actively pursuing employment, you feel it.", "answer_tokens": ["Perhaps", "that", "'s", "true", ",", "but", "if", "you", "'re", "one", "of", "the", "8", "percent", "who", "are", "unemployed", "and", "are", "actively", "pursuing", "employment", ",", "you", "feel", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Is that a valid point to make?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "valid", "point", "to", "make", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I think it's a valid point to make.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "valid", "point", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, I think there's a normal reaction, especially among us parents.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "normal", "reaction", ",", "especially", "among", "us", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Did you know how many of the last 60 mass shootings have been in gun-free zones?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "how", "many", "of", "the", "last", "60", "mass", "shootings", "have", "been", "in", "gun-free", "zones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "If I had to sit and count, I can tell you almost all of them.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "had", "to", "sit", "and", "count", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "almost", "all", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "But tell me this, I mean, do you go along then with this idea that you should arm almost everybody, at schools, at movie theaters?", "question_tokens": ["But", "tell", "me", "this", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "go", "along", "then", "with", "this", "idea", "that", "you", "should", "arm", "almost", "everybody", ",", "at", "schools", ",", "at", "movie", "theaters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "I mean, but where do you draw the line?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "but", "where", "do", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "But why would your answer to bringing down that statistic which presumably we all want to do, why would the answer then be more guns?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "would", "your", "answer", "to", "bringing", "down", "that", "statistic", "which", "presumably", "we", "all", "want", "to", "do", ",", "why", "would", "the", "answer", "then", "be", "more", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WDT", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Let me answer -- let me answer your question.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "answer", "--", "let", "me", "answer", "your", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "-- why would the way to bring down those numbers be to have even more guns?", "question_tokens": ["--", "why", "would", "the", "way", "to", "bring", "down", "those", "numbers", "be", "to", "have", "even", "more", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "You are not going to bring down suicide numbers by having less guns.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "not", "going", "to", "bring", "down", "suicide", "numbers", "by", "having", "less", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "It was a shotgun, I think?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "shotgun", ",", "I", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Do you need to have an assault weapon, an AR-15 military style rifle or do you believe that you were armed enough to do what you did, to defend yourself and your property and your family?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "need", "to", "have", "an", "assault", "weapon", ",", "an", "AR-15", "military", "style", "rifle", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "you", "were", "armed", "enough", "to", "do", "what", "you", "did", ",", "to", "defend", "yourself", "and", "your", "property", "and", "your", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes, in this particular case, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "in", "this", "particular", "case", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "How do we get through it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "get", "through", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "You know, I mean, that's a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Rifle Association"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "And where can you see at least some kind of consensus?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "can", "you", "see", "at", "least", "some", "kind", "of", "consensus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "A member of the National Rifle Association, at the very beginning, said that we ought to include people who have been adjudicated as mentally unstable in the national -- in the list of people who can't get guns.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "member", "of", "the", "National", "Rifle", "Association", ",", "at", "the", "very", "beginning", ",", "said", "that", "we", "ought", "to", "include", "people", "who", "have", "been", "adjudicated", "as", "mentally", "unstable", "in", "the", "national", "--", "in", "the", "list", "of", "people", "who", "ca", "n't", "get", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Do you own a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "own", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What do you have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "A shotgun.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "shotgun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Mark, do you have a gun?", "question_tokens": ["Mark", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Department"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Do you believe that there's compelling evidence that an assault weapons ban, if it removed the loopholes that were there last time, would have no effect, zero effect?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "there", "'s", "compelling", "evidence", "that", "an", "assault", "weapons", "ban", ",", "if", "it", "removed", "the", "loopholes", "that", "were", "there", "last", "time", ",", "would", "have", "no", "effect", ",", "zero", "effect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Well, the government studies -- the Justice Department studies about the previous gun ban said it had no effect.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "government", "studies", "--", "the", "Justice", "Department", "studies", "about", "the", "previous", "gun", "ban", "said", "it", "had", "no", "effect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "And you were shot, too?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "were", "shot", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I was not shot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "not", "shot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "One, I have no problem if you have guns in your home.", "answer_tokens": ["One", ",", "I", "have", "no", "problem", "if", "you", "have", "guns", "in", "your", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan", "Australia", "Britain"]}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Don't people watch \"Die Hard\" movies?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "people", "watch", "``", "Die", "Hard", "''", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "What many Americans don't realize is many countries around the world have brought in tough gun control, Japan, Australia, Britain and others.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "many", "Americans", "do", "n't", "realize", "is", "many", "countries", "around", "the", "world", "have", "brought", "in", "tough", "gun", "control", ",", "Japan", ",", "Australia", ",", "Britain", "and", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "And that involves if they want to get married in America, getting married?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "involves", "if", "they", "want", "to", "get", "married", "in", "America", ",", "getting", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Piers, when the president says half the things he says, I'm not sure what he means by them.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "when", "the", "president", "says", "half", "the", "things", "he", "says", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "what", "he", "means", "by", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Doesn't that bother you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "that", "bother", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "It bothers me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "bothers", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "But does that mean the climate is changing scientifically?", "question_tokens": ["But", "does", "that", "mean", "the", "climate", "is", "changing", "scientifically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Not climate, so to speak, but the weather day to day seems to be changing.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "climate", ",", "so", "to", "speak", ",", "but", "the", "weather", "day", "to", "day", "seems", "to", "be", "changing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Why am I taking a risk with my kids' and their kids' lives?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "am", "I", "taking", "a", "risk", "with", "my", "kids", "'", "and", "their", "kids", "'", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Well, that's a very good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "What do you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "1970S, we had global cooling.", "answer_tokens": ["1970S", ",", "we", "had", "global", "cooling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "What is your view, global warming?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", ",", "global", "warming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130122pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Frank?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Seems to me the bulk of evidence supports climate change.", "answer_tokens": ["Seems", "to", "me", "the", "bulk", "of", "evidence", "supports", "climate", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]